

### **CONTACTS**

Minsk, Belarus

+375(29)6737963

kavgorenya\_a@tut.by

in <u>nastassia\_kavgorenya</u>

KauhareniaNastassia

**%** KauhareniaNastassia

Portfolio

### **LANGUAGES**

English B1 (in progress)

Belarusian Native Russian Native

### **SKILLS**

React/Redux

JavaScript

Typescript

HTML/CSS

TDD/Storybook

Axios/Rest API

Thunk

React Hooks

Git/GitHub

Jira

Confluence

Figma

Miro

# Nastassia Kauharenia

## Front-end developer

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a front-end developer with huge interest in programming. I have an experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/ TypeScript in team. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies, for example, I'm planning to learn Angular. I also have an experience in design, I was studing UX/UI design.

I spend my leisure time reading literature and articles about development, watching video tutorials on YouTube about React and JS.

Open for your suggestions.

### **EXPERIENCE**

May 2022 - present My projects as front-end developer

(Part time)

#### Cards

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI, CSS, Formic; Created learning app in team with using git, worked with Axios(CRUD), bug fixing.

Social Network (in the process)

Stack: React, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI for some components, CSS, SCSS, Formic; Created educational project, organized correct app architecture, bug fixing, refactoring,

deploying.

Todolist

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Redux-Thunk, React-Router-dom, Axios, MUI, CSS, Storybook, Unit test for some components;

Created project with react hooks, routing and redirects, material UI, REST api request/response flow, unit-tests and etc., bug fixing.

June 2019-December 2022

LLC «Сладкое Дело» (Full time)

Lead decorator

- product design
- master classes
- customer security control
- · managing a team of 6 people
- taking part in the development of thematic collections
- training new staff
- monitoring consumables and ordering new ones

### **EDUCATION**

2021-2022 IT-Incubator
Front-end developer
React/Redux/JS/TS

2021-2022 Educational Platform Skillbox

Layout designer

HTML/CSS

2021-2022 IT-school TeachMeSkills

UX/UI designer

2011-2015 **Belarusian State Economic University** 

Faculty of Marketing and Logistics

Marketing specialist